[Applause]
[Music]
part
two directions you will hear a question
or statement and three responses spoken
in English they will not be printed in
your textbook and will be spoken only
one time select the best response to the
question or statement and mark the
letter A B or C on your answer
sheet now let's begin with question
number
seven number seven who is supposed to
participate in the marketing
seminar a it was Mr Santos's
idea B anyone who's
interested C the registration fee is
free number eight why wasn't this report
sent to Mr Wang
a it needs to be reviewed
first B because the reporter isn't here
yet C sure I could send it to
him number nine when did contractors get
here a early this
morning B sign at the bottom of the page
C it will take about a
week number 10 what's in those boxes we
have received
today a let's put them in different
boxes B new offer supplies we had
ordered C you should send them right
away
number
11 I'd like to cancel my reservation
please
a sorry we don't have any tables
available B may I have your name
please C sure the number is 5551
1212 number 12 do you know where the
orientation is being
held a sure follow
me B it'll be finished in an
hour C yes let's organize a
party number
13 would you like to take this yourself
or do you want it to be
delivered a I can't take the
bus B B I'll pick it up later
on C there will be some delivery
charge number
14 this is the key to the stock room
isn't
it a no use the one with a blue
tag B no the sales are over
now
C yes let's put them in the stock
room number
15 who is supporting this charity
function a the machine is
malfunctioning B it will be held in the
Marriott
Hotel C Georgia Foundation
is number
16 have all the guests arrived yet a
they're waiting in the other
room B my guess is as good as
yours C there is a musical performance
in the
theater number
17 the show begins at 8:00 doesn't
it a he's a great
performer B we should take the next
flight C the time should be on the
ticket number 18 how often do you attend
the company's professional
seminars a whenever I have
time B about the sales projection
C I'd love to
participate number
19 which company should we select to
provide food for our company
event a we have a variety of
selections B the Loretta catering did a
good job
before c it'll be held next Sunday
number
20 haven't you read that novel
before
a yes but I liked it so much I'm reading
it
again B no I've never met him
before c it was the best movie I've ever
seen number 21
is the convenience store on Main Street
open 24 hours a
day a when would be convenient for
you B no we have to make the reservation
in
advance
C yes but it closes on some
holidays number 22 I just found out that
our flight has been delayed
a for how
long B no I couldn't find it C let's
meet at the
lobby number
23 why weren't you at the budget meeting
for the
board a there was an emergency at the
Omaha
Branch b the meeting was held at the
main conference room
C sure I'll look over the figures one
more
time number
24 haven't you booked your flight to
Milwaukee
yet a yes the airport has been
changed B actually I just did
it C it was announced just
yesterday
number
25 have you contacted the insurance
agency or do you want me to call
them a no I didn't like the terms in the
contract B did you use the right
number c I already had a talk with
them number 26
why don't we use an electric screwdriver
to assemble the
table a I have one in my tool
box B I prefer to go
alone
C the appliance should be stored in the
back number
27 could you hand out conference
materials to the participants waiting at
the registration
a there will be a $50
fee B I'm afraid I won't be able
to
C thanks but I already have
one number
28 we should check the inventory before
we order more
merchandise a yes the technician will be
here
soon B we have a fully equipped
facility C I'll have it done right
away number 29 there's no more paper in
the supply
cabinet
a Maria is in charge of keeping it
stocked B who used the lasting
cartridge C I read in the newspaper this
morning number 30 why don't we start on
the marketing project
today a the market doesn't open on the
weekends
B I think she is the new project
leader C actually the budget analysis
needs to be done
first
number 31 didn't Amy Peterson do a great
job of representing our firm at the
convention a I didn't get the job I
wanted
B yes let's register for the seminar
right
away
see yes she is an effective
presenter
number seven who is supposed to
participate in the marketing
seminar a it was Mr Santos's
idea B anyone who's
interested C the registration fee is
free number eight why wasn't this report
sent to Mr
hang a it needs to be reviewed
first B because the reporter isn't here
yet see sure I could send it to
him
number nine when did contractors get
here a early this
morning B sign at the bottom of the
page C it will take about a
week number 10 what's in those boxes we
have received
today a
let's put them in different
boxes B new office supplies we had
ordered C you should send them right
away number
11 I'd like to cancel my reservation
please
a sorry we don't have any tables
available B may I have your name
please C sure the number is 5551
1212 number 12 do you know where the
orientation is being
held a sure follow
me B it'll be finished in an
hour C yes let's organize a
party
number
13 would you like to take this yourself
or do you want it to be
delivered a I can't take the
bus B I'll pick it up later
on C there will be some delivery
charge number
14 this is the key to the stock room
isn't
it a no use the one with a blue
tag B no the sales are over
now
C yes let's put them in the stock
room number
15 who is supporting this charity
function a the machine is malfunctioning
B it will be held in the Marriott
Hotel C Georgia Foundation
is number
16 have all the guests arrived
yet a they're waiting in the other
room B my guess is as good as
yours C there is a musical performance
in the
theater number
17 the show begins at 8:00 doesn't
it a he's a great
performer B we should take the next
flight C the time should be on the
ticket
number 18 how often do you attend the
company's professional
seminars a whenever I have
time B about the sales
projection C I'd love to
participate number
19 which company should we select to
provide food for our company event
a we have a variety of
selections B the Loretta catering did a
good job
before c it'll be held next
Sunday number
20 haven't you read that novel
before
a yes but I liked it so much I'm reading
it
again
B no I've never met him
before c it was the best movie I've ever
seen number
21 is the convenience store on Main
Street open 24 hours a
day a when would be convenient for
you B no we have to make the reservation
in advance
C yes but it closes on some
holidays number 22 I just found out that
our flight has been
delayed a for how
long B no I couldn't find it C let's
meet at the
lobby number 23 why weren't you at the
budget meeting for the
board a there was an emergency at the
Omaha
Branch b the meeting was held at the
main conference
room C sure I'll look over the figures
one more
time number
24 haven't you booked your flight to
Milwaukee yet
a yes the airport has been
changed B actually I just did
it C it was announced just
yesterday number
25 have you contacted the insurance
agency or do you want me to call
them a no I didn't like the terms in the
contract
B did you use the right
number c I already had a talk with
them number
26 why don't we use an electric
screwdriver to assemble the
table a I have one in my
toolbox B I prefer to go
alone C the appliance should be stored
in the
back number
27 could you hand out conference
materials to the participants waiting at
the
registration a there will be a $50
fee B I'm afraid I won't be able
to
C thanks but I already have
one
number
28 we should check the inventory before
we order more
merchandise a yes the technician will be
here
soon B we have a fully equipped
facility C I'll have it done right
away number 29 there's no more paper in
the supply
cabinet a Maria is in charge of keeping
it
stocked B who used the lasting
cartridge C I read it in the newspaper
this
morning number 30 why don't we start on
the marketing project
today a the market doesn't open on the
weekends
B I think she is the new project
leader C actually the budget analysis
needs to be done
first number 31 didn't Amy Peterson do a
great job of representing our firm at
the
convention a I didn't get the job I
wanted B
yes let's register for the seminar right
away
see yes she is an effective
presenter
that